Guide to the Michael Letwin Papers TAM.464
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Subject Files, 2010 Accession, 1978-2007; 310381; 29 Linear Feet
  - New York City Police Department, undated; 310384; 10 Linear Feet
    - New York City Police Department 10, 1983 - 2001; 311107 (Box 32)
      Contains: Allan Cameroon, 2005; Shooting by year; Tysheen Bourne and Thomas Boyland, 2000; Reynaldo Colon, 2000; Malcolm Ferguson, 2000; Carmen Valentine, 2000; Andre Austin, 9/18/1999; Gary Busch, 8/30/1999; Larry Cobb, 8/18/99; Stanton Crew, 1999; Walter Hickey, 2/23/1999; Dantae Johnson, 5/26/1999; Charles Stevens, 4/6/1999; Robert Striker, 8/9/1999; Richard Watson, 9/1/1999; Dexter Brown, 1998; Sean Kelly, 9/31/1998; Michael Jones, 1998; Antonio Reid, 6/14/1998; Felix River, 1/1983; Steven Service, 2/27/1998; Jason Rodriguez, 1995; Anthony Rosario, 1/12/95; Argencio, 1/1994; Desmond Robinson, 8/22/1994; Kenneth Cook, 1993; Aurea Bonnie Vargas, 1/29/1993; Earl Black, 5/27/1992; Robert Cabeza, 1992; Jacques Camille, 4/9/1992; Jose Garcia, 7/3/1992; Douglas Orfaly, 3/3/1992; P.O. Derwin Pannell, 11/17/1992; Ardel Amos, 8/25/1991; David Coho, 3/1/1990; Jose Cruz, 12/7/1990; Jose Luis Lebron, 2/1/1990; Luis Liranzo, 1/27/1990; Patrick Bailey, 10/31/1997; Reginald Bannerman, 12/1997; Kevin Cedeno, 4/1997; Donald Davidson, 3/1997; Rodney Dilbert, 1997; William Whitfield, 12/1997; Charles Campbell, 10/1996; Nathaniel Levi Gaines, 7/1996; Gayle Hoffman, 3/1996; Henry Phelan, 1/1996; Thompkins Square Park [riot], 1988
  - Racism, undated; 310385; 1 Linear Feet (1 box)
    - Racism, 1980 - 2002; 311109 (Box 33)
      Contains: Atlanta murders - Wayne Williams; Greensboro, NC murders, 1979; Latinos, immigration; Klan; Attica Prison (NYS); Martin Luther King; Muslims; Malcolm X; Political prisoners, misc.; Repression, US; MOVE; Mumia Abu Jamal
  - Racist Violence, 311042 (Box 34)
    - Racist Violence, 1980 - 1989; 311110 (Box 34)
      Contains: Central Park jogger 4/89; Bernard Goetz, 1984; Yusef Hawkins, 1989; Howard Beach, 1986; 1980-1989; Willie Turks, June 1982; Crown Heights (Bklyn, NY)